thenextwomen.com 2018-08-24

# Privacy Policy – TheNextWomen

PRIVACY POLICY of INFO PUBLISHERS B.V.

INTRODUCTION  
TheNextWomen takes your privacy very seriously and will process and use information about you (the data subject) in a secure manner. In this Privacy Statement we explain which data we process and for which purpose we do so. In addition, in this Privacy Statement you can read about your rights regarding our processing of your personal data. We encourage you to read this Privacy Statement carefully. For questions you can always contact info@thenextwomen.com.

WHO IS THENEXTWOMEN?  
TheNextWomen is the private limited company Info Publishers B.V., with offices at (1071 NT) Amsterdam at De Lairessestraat 55, registered in the trade register of the Chamber of Commerce under number 16085674.

TheNextWomen is the controller with regard to the processing of your personal data by TheNextWomen.

—- SECTION 1 – HOW DOES THENEXTWOMEN USE YOUR DATA?

Below is an overview of the purposes for which TheNextWomen processes personal data about you. In doing so, it is always indicated which data TheNextWomen uses for that specific purpose, which is the legal basis for processing that data and for how long the data is retained by TheNextWomen. To keep things organized, we have grouped everything by type of data stream.

SERVICES, CUSTOMER MANAGEMENT AND FINANCIAL ADMINISTRATION  
Purpose: Financial administration  
Data: Company name, Invoice address, Bank details (Bank name / IBAN / BIC), Outstanding balance  
Basis: Legal obligation  
Retention period: As long as necessary for this purpose

Purpose: Management of orders  
Data: Invoice address, E-mail address, Telephone number, Payment details  
Basis: Implementation of the agreement  
Retention period: As long as necessary for this purpose

Purpose: Invoicing  
Data: Invoice address, E-mail address, Telephone number, Payment details  
Basis: Implementation of the agreement  
Retention period: As long as necessary for this purpose

Purpose: To provide the service itself  
Data: E-mail address, Data required to provide the service, Data generated during the service  
Basis: Implementation of the agreement  
Retention period: As long as necessary for this purpose

Purpose: Invoicing  
Data: E-mail address, Data required to provide the service, Data generated during the service  
Basis: Implementation of the agreement  
Retention period: As long as necessary for this purpose Purpose: CRM

Data: Name, User name, E-mail address, Order history, OS, Telephone number, Profile photo  
Basis: Justified interest  
Relevant interest: Commercial interest  
Retention period: As long as necessary for this purpose

MARKETING  
Purpose: Direct marketing  
Data: Name, E-mail addressBasis: Justified interest  
Relevant interest: Commercial interest  
Retention period: As long as necessary for this purpose

Purpose: Newsletter  
Data: Name, E-mail address  
Basis: Justified interest  
Relevant interest: Commercial interest  
Retention period: As long as necessary for this purpose

Purpose: Social marketing  
Data: Name, E-mail address  
Basis: Justified interest  
Relevant interest: Commercial interest  
Retention period: As long as necessary for this purpose

WEBSITE  
Purpose: Website analytics  
Data: Surfing behavior  
Basis: Justified interest  
Relevant interest: Commercial interest  
Retention period: As long as necessary for this purpose

Purpose: Posting of messages or reviews  
Data: Name, Username  
Basis: Implementation of the agreement  
Retention period: As long as necessary for this purpose

SECURITY AND FRAUD PREVENTION  
Purpose: Data security  
Data: Financial transactions, Name  
Basis: Justified interest  
Relevant interest: Commercial interest  
Retention period: As long as necessary for this purpose

RESEARCH & DEVELOPMENT  
Purpose: Market research  
Data: E-mail address, Telephone number, Information about the behavior  
Basis: Justified interest  
Relevant interest: Commercial interest  
Retention period: As long as necessary for this purpose

SECTION 2 – CONSENT

HOW DO WE OBTAIN YOUR PERSONAL DATA?  
TheNextWomen has data about you because you have provided that information to us.

WHAT ARE YOUR RIGHTS?  
Under the European General Data Protection Regulation you have a number of rights with regard to your data and their processing:

INSIGHT  
You can always view your own (personal) data and change it in your account if necessary. If you want to see the personal data that has been recorded about You at TheNextWomen, you can request access to it.

MODIFY  
If you wish to make changes to the personal data that you have seen as a result of a request for access and that you can not change yourself in your account, you can request this at TheNextWomen. You can request that TheNextWomen modify, correct, supplement, delete or protect your data.

LIMITING THE PROCESSING  
You also have the right, subject to conditions, to request TheNextWomen to limit the processing of your personal data. Right of objectionIf a certain processing takes place on the grounds of the ‘legitimate interest’ of TheNextWomen or a third party, you have the right to object to that processing.

DATA TRANSFER  
You have the right to obtain your personal data from TheNextWomen. TheNextWomen will provide this in a structured and current form, which can easily be opened in other common digital systems. This way you can also transfer your data to another provider.

RETRACT PERMISSION  
In all cases in which the basis for a certain data processing is your consent, you have the right to revoke that permission. This has no consequences for the past, but does mean that we will no longer be allowed to process this data. It may be that TheNextWomen can no longer provide you with certain services.

RESPONSE BY THENEXTWOMEN  
A request can be sent to info@thenextwomen.com. TheNextWomen will comply with your request as soon as possible and in any case no later than one (1) month after TheNextWomen has received such a request. If TheNextWomen rejects your request, we will indicate in our reply why the request is rejected.

SECTION 3 – DISCLOSURE

RECIPIENTS OF PERSONAL DATA  
The data can be passed on to:  
Parties that are involved in the execution or fulfillment of an agreement between you and TheNextWomen  
It may be that TheNextWomen is obliged to provide your data to a third party, for example on the basis of a legal obligation.

SECTION 4 – SISOW

Payment:

If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Sisow stores your credit card data. It is encrypted. Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.

For more insight, you may also want to read Sisow’s Terms and conditions [here](https://www.sisow.nl/algemeen/algemene_voorwaarden).

SECTION 5 – THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are located in the Netherlands and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United Kingdom, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United Kingdom legislation.

Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms and Conditions.

Links

When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

Google analytics:

Our store uses Google Analytics to help us learn about who visits our site and what pages are being looked at.

SECTION 6 – SECURITY

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

SECTION 7 – AGE OF CONSENT

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your country, state, or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

SECTION 8 – CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

SECTION 9 – WHERE CAN YOU GO WITH YOUR COMPLAINTS AND QUESTIONS?

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement and the way in which TheNextWomen uses your data, you can send an e-mail to info@thenextwomen.com. Even if you have a complaint about how TheNextWomen processes your data, you can send an e-mail to info@thenextwomen.com. You can also always contact the competent national supervisor in the field of privacy protection. In the Netherlands this is the Dutch Data Protection Authority

Info Publishers B.V., De Lairessestraat 55, 1071NT Amsterdam
